clubcareinsurance.co.uk 2008-12-27

# Caravan Insurance | Club Care Insurance - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY / LEGAL DISCLAIMER

VISL Privacy Policy provides information regarding accuracy, access, security and how it manages visitor, supplier and client information collected from its Website(s).

### Vantage Insurance Services Ltd (VISL) Website mission:

The mission of the VISL website is to furnish visitors, suppliers and clients with the most current product and company information and present it in a manner that best benefits their needs. VISL Insurance Website may be accessed by all Internet users on a 24/7 basis. 

### Interruptions and Omissions in Service:

Whilst we try to ensure that the standard of this Website remains high and to maintain the continuity of it, the internet is not an inherently stable medium, and errors, omissions, interruptions of service and delays may occur at any time. We do not accept any liability arising from any such errors, omissions, interruptions or delays or any ongoing obligation or responsibility to operate this Website (or any particular part of it) or to provide the service offered on this Website. We may vary the specification of this site from time to time without notice. 

### What are 'cookies' and why do we use them?:

'Cookies' are ways of saving a small amount of personal information. We only use them to save your user name or password to allow easy access to our site. We advise you not to use 'cookies' if your computer is shared by other people.

### Information Submitted by You:

We will process any data which you provide in completing the online registration or application forms and any further forms containing company and personal details which you complete or provide to us when using this site in accordance with UK data protection legislation. 

### How is this data safeguarded?:

The security of your data is extremely important to us. Access to your company and your personal data is only provided to our staff. We only pass information about you or your company to third parties where necessary to fulfil our obligations to you.

### Your Use of our Web Site:

You may only use this Site for lawful purposes when seeking information. You must not under any circumstances seek to undermine the security of the Site or any information submitted to or available through it. In particular, but without limitation, you must not seek to access, alter or delete any information to which you do not have authorised access, seek to overload the system via spamming or flooding, take any action or use any device, routine or software to crash, delay, damage or otherwise interfere with the operation of this Site or attempt to decipher, disassemble or modify any of the software, coding or information comprised in the Site. 

### Information on our Web Site:

Whilst we make every effort to ensure that the information on this site is accurate and complete, some of the information is supplied to us by third parties and we are not able to check the accuracy or completeness of that information. We do not accept any liability arising from any inaccuracy or omission in any of the information on our web site or any liability in respect of information on our web site supplied by you, any other site user or any other person.

### Choice of Law and Jurisdiction:

The use of this Website and any agreements entered into through this Website are to be governed by and construed in accordance with English law. The courts of England are to have exclusive jurisdiction to settle any dispute arising out of or in connection with the use of this Website or any agreement made through this Website.

### Terminology:

**Data** \- information which is being processed by equipment operating automatically in response to instructions given for that purpose, is recorded with the intention that it should be processed by means of such equipment, is recorded as part of a relevant filing system or with the intention that it should form part of a relevant filing system or forms part of an accessible record.

**Data Protection Acts 1984 and 1998** \- these are the Acts of Parliament which set out principles relating to the use of data to ensure that the rights of the person who is the subject of the data are protected under the law.

**Personal data** \- data which relates to a living individual who can be identified from those data, or from those data and other information which is in the possession of, or is likely to come into the possession of, VISL.

**Privacy policy** \- this is a statement by VISL which explains the ways that we try to protect our users' privacy. 

**Third Parties** \- these are companies and people other than VISL and the group of companies of which it is part. 

**Users** \- people who use our Website and register their details with us for the purposes of commenting about our site, gain more information and general business use.

VISL is a trading name of Vantage Insurance Services Limited ("VISL"). VISL is a subsidiary of Kerry London. 

Registered Office: 7 Birchin Lane, London EC3V 9BW. Registered No. 3441136.
